>> Brian Holt: 我现在想做的是我们已经把这个项目写在
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what I wanna do now is
we have this project that we've written in
只是香草的 JavaScript
just vanilla JavaScript.
我想你们很多人都在
And I imagine many of you
are working in places that
当前不在 TypeScript 中，但您希望它在 TypeScript 中，对吗 ?
are not currently in TypeScript, but
you'd like it to be in TypeScript, right?
但这意味着移民。
But that means a migration.
所以你和我今天要做的就是把我们的整个计划
So what you and I are gonna do today is
we're gonna migrate our entire project to
TypeScript 非常快。
TypeScript really quick.
只是为了让你知道你有点痛苦
Just to show you that
t's a little painful,
有点烦人但这是很有可能的
it's a little annoying, but
it's very possible, okay?
所以我们开始吧开始吧
So let's go ahead and get started.
所以我就在这里的雷波里我在总行
So I'm in my repo here,
I'm in the master branch,
我会说 npm install -D typescript。
and I'm gonna say npm
install -D typescript.
所以我从下午 3 点 4 分收到了 TypeScript
So I got TypeScript off of npm 3.4 and
之后我就会说
I'm going to say after that,
npx，它是一个将为您运行 npm 二进制文件的工具。
npx, which is a tool that's going
to run npm binaries for you.
tsc，即 TypeSript 编译器， --init。
tsc, which is the TypeSript compiler,
--init.
所以这将为我们启动一个 TypeScript 项目，好吗 ?
So this going to start
a TypeScript project for us, okay?
那么现在如果你去看 tsconfig，我就是为你创造的，
So now if you go look at tsconfig,
which I just generated for you,
你把这件事都搞明白了
you get this whole thing of tsconfig.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 你和我有几件事要做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So there's a couple things
that you and I are gonna have to do here.
我们的目标是 ES2019
Our target is going to be ES2019, or
18岁或者不管你想做什么
18, or whatever you want it to be.
看来不像 19岁了让我们说 18吧
Looks like it doesn't like 19,
so let's say 18.
> > Brian Holt: 那么最后一个要做的就是在这里保存 jsx ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then the last one you
have to do is preserve jsx right here,
取消注释并作出反应。
uncomment that one and put react.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 是的，我们走了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, there we go.
其他的你都想保持相对
Everything else,
you wanna leave relatively the same,
此处的大键是 "strict": true。
The big key here one is "strict": true.
让我们先讲严格的模式。
Let's talk about strict mode for
just a second.
如果你要在 TypeScript 中启动一个全新的项目
If you're gonna just start out with
a brand new project in TypeScript, and
你想按你的速度尽快开始
you wanna just get started
as fast as you can,
您可以使用 "strict" 引入 TypeScript : false。
you can introduce TypeScript
with "strict": false.
这会让它更容易入门。
And this is going to make it
a lot easier to get started.
但你却没有得到好处对吧
But you get less of the benefit, right?
更严格的是你的类型检查，你得到的好处就越多，
The stricter you are with your type
checking, the more benefit you get, and
更烦人的是吧 ?
also the more annoying it is, right?
所以它更有好处，但也会痛得更多。
So it's more beneficial,
but it also hurts more.
所以我会说 " 严格"，可能是假的 ?
So I would say go ahead and
start out with "strict": false, maybe?
但你应该总是采取严格的方式
But you should always
get to strict mode true.
假只是一个踏踏踏石的踏脚石。
False is only a stepping stone to true.
你总是想实现真正的
You always wanna get to true.
所以我们要从真实的开始我们才会继续
So we're gonna start with true, and
we're just gonna stay with true.
我们接下来要做的就是
The next thing that we need to do is,
类似 React 的包不会在 TypeScript 中写入，对吗 ?
packages like React are not
written in TypeScript, right?
它们是由不使用 TypeScript的其他团队编写的。
They're written by a different
team that doesn't use TypeScript.
但是当我们使用 " React" 时，我们希望具有类型。
However, we wanna have
types when we use React.
幸好有个叫 DefinitelyTyped 的项目
Luckily there's a project
called DefinitelyTyped
允许人们为他们无法控制的图书馆写类型
that allows people to write types for
libraries that they don't control.
然后我们可以把它们导入到我们的项目中，对吧 ?
And then we can import them
into our project, right?
这就是 React所发生的事情。
So that's what happened with React.
所以我们能做的就是
So what we can do in
here is we can come and
说 npm 安装 -D @types/ 反应，对吗 ?
say npm install -D @types/react, right?
因此尽管 React 不是在 TypeScript中写入的，
So despite the fact that React
is not written in TypeScript,
我们还可以通过安装这个包来获取类型。
we can still get types out of
it by installing this package.
然后我们会做 @types/ 反反派
And then we'll do @types/react-dom and
@types/ 反应。
@types/react.
也不能用反斜杠让你双下划线
And it can't do slashes so
you do double underscore so
类型 /可达性路由器。
types/reach__router.
>> Brian Holt: Right， cuz 通常是 @reach/router。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right,
cuz normally it's @reach/router.
>> Brian Holt: 这将为我们提供这些项目的所有类型。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And this'll give us
all the types for these projects.
>> Brian Holt: 其他项目如 FrontEndMaster/Pet one，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So other projects
like the FrontEndMaster/Pet one,
它已经有自己的类型定义了
it already has its own type
definitions that ship with it.
所以你不用装类型就有了
So you don't have to install types for
it, it just has them and
就有了这个项目
it comes with the project.
>> Brian Holt: 但现在我们可以使用所有这些类型。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But now we have all
of these types that we can use.